[
  {
    "id": "71991741-8748-4057-88c1-c852e80a40ae",
    "reference": "1- Ezekiel 33:7 \u201cI have made you a watchman\u201d",
    "question": "Who was appointed as the watchman over the house of Israel?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "John",
      "Ezekiel",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Ezekiel",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "54bd2013-9b76-4c96-9ed8-a8cd5a14bfc9",
    "reference": "1- Ezekiel 33:7 \u201cI have made you a watchman\u201d",
    "question": "What might happen to the watchman if he does not warn the wicked as recommender by the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "He would give an account to the Lord if the wicked does not repent",
      "It depends on every individual case",
      "The wicked would blame the watchman on the judgment\u2019s day"
    ],
    "answer": "He would give an account to the Lord if the wicked does not repent",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "676e0bc4-10d9-4a64-a6d4-ac6b5eb479d5",
    "reference": "2- Hosea 4:6 \u201cMy people are destroyed for lack of knowledge\u201d",
    "question": "Say unto them, as I live, saith the Lord God, I have no ___ in the death of the wicked",
    "options": [
      "Hand",
      "Compassion",
      "Knowledge",
      "Pleasure"
    ],
    "answer": "Pleasure",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f6240327-cbec-4636-b546-93418fd11832",
    "reference": "2- Hosea 4:6 \u201cMy people are destroyed for lack of knowledge\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Hosea\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Uzziah",
      "Jotham",
      "Beeri",
      "Jeroboam"
    ],
    "answer": "Beeri",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c541bdb0-8acb-4fc2-aee0-2374a9682d96",
    "reference": "2- Hosea 4:6 \u201cMy people are destroyed for lack of knowledge\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord hath a controversy with the inhabitants of the land, because there is no __, no mercy, nor knowledge of God in the land.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Understanding",
      "Truth",
      "Patience"
    ],
    "answer": "Truth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fb4a08ba-2cac-4aa5-a592-514d77f45515",
    "reference": "3- Daniel 2:18-23 \u201c[God] changes the times and the seasons\u201d",
    "question": "And I will punish them for their ways, and ___ them their doings.",
    "options": [
      "Reward",
      "Prosper",
      "Protect",
      "Reduce"
    ],
    "answer": "Reward",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1b6c3eb0-b994-489f-88e7-d3698dc4395d",
    "reference": "3- Daniel 2:18-23 \u201c[God] changes the times and the seasons\u201d",
    "question": "Why did the king command to destroy all the wise men of Babylon?",
    "options": [
      "Because he felt they were no longer wise",
      "Because some of them lied to him",
      "Because they couldn\u2019t interpret the dream he had",
      "Because he didn\u2019t like them anymore"
    ],
    "answer": "Because they couldn\u2019t interpret the dream he had",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "93488d3c-f9d1-47fe-a893-f34aba916031",
    "reference": "3- Daniel 2:18-23 \u201c[God] changes the times and the seasons\u201d",
    "question": "How many companions did Daniel have?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "3",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e0925594-9d5e-455a-9cca-6c4457f92c3a",
    "reference": "4- Daniel 4:26 \u201cHeaven rules\u201d",
    "question": "How was the King\u2019s dream reveal to Daniel?",
    "options": [
      "Through prophesy",
      "Through teaching",
      "Through a night vision",
      "Through a day vision"
    ],
    "answer": "Through a night vision",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "267157af-9f80-4930-9231-ae4646b2a784",
    "reference": "4- Daniel 4:26 \u201cHeaven rules\u201d",
    "question": "What was the other name of Daniel?",
    "options": [
      "Jehoiakim",
      "Paul",
      "Belteshazzar",
      "Nebuchadnezzar"
    ],
    "answer": "Belteshazzar",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "defd5542-ab7a-40af-bb27-fc2fdd730a62",
    "reference": "4- Daniel 4:26 \u201cHeaven rules\u201d",
    "question": "His kingdom is an __ kingdom, and his dominion is from generation to generation",
    "options": [
      "Unpredictable",
      "Amazing",
      "Everlasting",
      "Awesome"
    ],
    "answer": "Everlasting",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "21aca862-4337-4442-9956-905349d67f43",
    "reference": "5- Daniel 5:21 \u201cThe Most High God rules in the kingdom of men\u201d",
    "question": "O king Nebuchadnezzar, to thee it is spoken; the kingdom is ___ from thee.",
    "options": [
      "Given",
      "Banished",
      "Departed",
      "Reported"
    ],
    "answer": "Departed",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0e760b36-bf11-49fd-a383-821e914aa1eb",
    "reference": "5- Daniel 5:21 \u201cThe Most High God rules in the kingdom of men\u201d",
    "question": "Why did King Belshazzar become terrified?",
    "options": [
      "Because he found out he would lose his kingdom",
      "Because he found out he would die",
      "Because he was ill",
      "Because the wise men could not read the writing"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the wise men could not read the writing",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "923dbcce-4043-446c-b214-1ac5f30d31f9",
    "reference": "5- Daniel 5:21 \u201cThe Most High God rules in the kingdom of men\u201d",
    "question": "What did the king promise Daniel if he read the writing?",
    "options": [
      "Give him a gold chain",
      "Clothes him in purple",
      "Make him the third highest ruler in the kingdom",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0681a402-19de-4b6d-bc79-b36dfaa55b1e",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "Nevertheless, brethren, I have written the more boldly unto you in some sort, as putting you in mind, because of the ___ that is given to me of God.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Fear",
      "Imagination",
      "Grace"
    ],
    "answer": "Grace",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9d7515f2-f2fb-4858-9def-fd3d936eb883",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed be the Lord God of __ from everlasting to everlasting: and let all the people say, Amen.",
    "options": [
      "Jacob",
      "Abraham",
      "Israel",
      "Our father"
    ],
    "answer": "Israel",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8655df4-bc55-42e9-b057-dcf07fc8b41d",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "For he __ the longing soul, and filleth the hungry soul with goodness",
    "options": [
      "Supply",
      "Provideth",
      "Satisfieth",
      "Listen"
    ],
    "answer": "Satisfieth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "34827278-95e3-408f-9d6d-8d7db5942117",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "He sent his word, and healed them, and __ them from their destructions",
    "options": [
      "Protected",
      "Blessed",
      "Delivered",
      "Supplied"
    ],
    "answer": "Delivered",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "37c8d854-91c3-4c87-ae69-4b49406b0ac3",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "Lift up your hands in the ___, and bless the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "House",
      "Sanctuary",
      "Synagogue",
      "Assembly"
    ],
    "answer": "Sanctuary",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6e64bb81-b227-4a17-a664-e7cc37088f75",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "His enemies will I clothe with __: but upon himself shall his crown flourish.",
    "options": [
      "Punishment",
      "Mockery",
      "Shame",
      "Slavery"
    ],
    "answer": "Shame",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4a0b749a-3b92-40d9-9166-011096224250",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "Thy name, O Lord, ___ for ever; and thy memorial, O Lord, throughout all generations",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Endureth",
      "Everlasting",
      "Known"
    ],
    "answer": "Endureth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "00860a93-a206-4d5f-86c7-34d8c46fd199",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "And he said unto me, Son of man, can these bones __?",
    "options": [
      "Be blessed",
      "Prosper",
      "Live",
      "Move"
    ],
    "answer": "Live",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2f006255-bc93-4198-8b22-ded6e81bd5ee",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 107:2 \u201cLet the redeemed of the LORD say so\u201d",
    "question": "Can the dry bones hear the word of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Sometimes",
      "Yes",
      "It depends on the quality of the bones"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c29d2b33-410d-48d9-905a-e50f01cb2166",
    "reference": "9- Joel 2:13 \u201cReturn to the LORD your God\u201d",
    "question": "What do the bones represent?",
    "options": [
      "Dead people",
      "Food",
      "The whole house of Israel",
      "Hidden treasures"
    ],
    "answer": "The whole house of Israel",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "23f82e28-2e29-4a3b-ab60-66c5aaa2eabd",
    "reference": "9- Joel 2:13 \u201cReturn to the LORD your God\u201d",
    "question": "How is the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "He is gracious",
      "He is merciful",
      "He is slow to anger",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7559d23a-4233-4f77-9535-0ff8e6f7fc85",
    "reference": "9- Joel 2:13 \u201cReturn to the LORD your God\u201d",
    "question": "Fear not, O land; be __ and rejoice: for the Lord will do great things",
    "options": [
      "Reassured",
      "Comforted",
      "Calm",
      "Glad"
    ],
    "answer": "Glad",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "335df391-9226-4f04-9162-4e88c5bdcd53",
    "reference": "10- Psalm 34:6 \u201cThe LORD heard him and saved him out of all his troubles\u201d",
    "question": "Then will the Lord be ___ for his land, and pity his people",
    "options": [
      "Furious",
      "Protective",
      "Jealous",
      "Angry"
    ],
    "answer": "Jealous",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "152e163f-1c76-40d1-b936-6e7ce085a20b",
    "reference": "10- Psalm 34:6 \u201cThe LORD heard him and saved him out of all his troubles\u201d",
    "question": "Let thy __, O Lord, be upon us, according as we hope in thee.",
    "options": [
      "Blessing",
      "Protection",
      "Mercy",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercy",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f284abd0-12b7-4205-8851-a770a0e13ccd",
    "reference": "10- Psalm 34:6 \u201cThe LORD heard him and saved him out of all his troubles\u201d",
    "question": "O fear the Lord, ye his saints: for there is no __ to them that fear him",
    "options": [
      "Want",
      "Desire",
      "Lack",
      "Shame"
    ],
    "answer": "Want",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "160a6633-6661-4fee-91f4-7ee1a621dc5f",
    "reference": "11- 1 Corinthians 10:13 \u201cNo temptation has overtaken you except such as is common to man\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord redeemeth the soul of his servants: and none of them that trust in him shall be ___",
    "options": [
      "Poor",
      "Alone",
      "Abandon",
      "Desolate"
    ],
    "answer": "Desolate",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3c39cdf0-4e0c-4b4a-91b0-b8008c1d1ee8",
    "reference": "11- 1 Corinthians 10:13 \u201cNo temptation has overtaken you except such as is common to man\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of 1 Corinthians?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "Paul",
      "John",
      "Jesus"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c6f9c2f9-cb21-4e1b-8de6-2eeb384d1e4e",
    "reference": "11- 1 Corinthians 10:13 \u201cNo temptation has overtaken you except such as is common to man\u201d",
    "question": "And were all baptized unto ___ in the cloud and in the sea",
    "options": [
      "Lord",
      "Jesus",
      "Moses",
      "King"
    ],
    "answer": "Moses",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ef6053d8-467e-4808-a425-eaa99ed8d3d9",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 55:10 -11 \u201c[My Word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "Wherefore, my dearly beloved, flee from ___?",
    "options": [
      "Idolatry",
      "Lust",
      "Lie",
      "Gossip"
    ],
    "answer": "Idolatry",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0270ec34-fb35-4baa-b7e0-277400c65641",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 55:10 -11 \u201c[My Word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "Seek ye the Lord while he may be ___, call ye upon him while he is near.",
    "options": [
      "Known",
      "Found",
      "Remembered",
      "Seen"
    ],
    "answer": "Found",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "586836a9-9c1a-4e0a-b3ce-bb01a30443ea",
    "reference": "12- Isaiah 55:10 -11 \u201c[My Word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "How are the thoughts of the Lord compare to ours?",
    "options": [
      "Same",
      "Righteous",
      "Higher",
      "Great"
    ],
    "answer": "Higher",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7a66f96d-c9c8-4d45-8344-0dab6b1271af",
    "reference": "13- Psalm 37:1 \u201cDo not fret because of evildoers\u201d",
    "question": "No weapon that is formed against you shall ___?",
    "options": [
      "Live",
      "Be effective",
      "Harm you",
      "Prosper?"
    ],
    "answer": "Prosper?",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "65ae9474-cb46-4105-bd50-6abc2080ec52",
    "reference": "13- Psalm 37:1 \u201cDo not fret because of evildoers\u201d",
    "question": "Cease from __, and forsake wrath: fret not thyself in any wise to do evil",
    "options": [
      "Malice",
      "Scandal",
      "Anger",
      "Envy"
    ],
    "answer": "Anger",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7254849c-0ea2-4dbe-8068-5396a7a8fe80",
    "reference": "13- Psalm 37:1 \u201cDo not fret because of evildoers\u201d",
    "question": "Trust in the Lord, and do __: so shalt thou dwell in the land, and verily thou shalt be fed",
    "options": [
      "Sacrifice",
      "Wonders",
      "Good",
      "Miracle"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b564d593-d615-4c95-9e23-bf1c99c3338c",
    "reference": "14- Jeremiah 24:7 \u201cI will give them a heart to know Me\u201d",
    "question": "The steps of a good man are ___ by the Lord: and he delighteth in his way",
    "options": [
      "Ordered",
      "Protected",
      "Enlighten",
      "Brighten"
    ],
    "answer": "Ordered",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7e70f7cc-e446-4cac-9c21-6db6d5cd8456",
    "reference": "14- Jeremiah 24:7 \u201cI will give them a heart to know Me\u201d",
    "question": "For I will set mine ___ upon them for good, and I will bring them again to this land",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Eyes",
      "Compassion",
      "Blessing"
    ],
    "answer": "Eyes",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f69c6e15-c666-4da2-be25-b156efa0d845",
    "reference": "15- Habakkuk 2:14 \u201cThe earth will be filled with the knowledge of the glory of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "And I will __ them to be removed into all the kingdoms of the earth for their hurt, to be a reproach and a proverb, a taunt and a curse, in all places whither I shall drive them",
    "options": [
      "Cause",
      "Instruct",
      "Deliver",
      "Ensure"
    ],
    "answer": "Deliver",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "306d72ad-32bb-4b99-9b21-cc42333cc757",
    "reference": "15- Habakkuk 2:14 \u201cThe earth will be filled with the knowledge of the glory of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Woe to him that buildeth a town with ___, and stablisheth a city by iniquity",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Blood",
      "Unction",
      "Cry"
    ],
    "answer": "Blood",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4196eaec-178b-4366-8a40-fddea560406c",
    "reference": "15- Habakkuk 2:14 \u201cThe earth will be filled with the knowledge of the glory of the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Write the __, and make it plain upon tables, that he may run that readeth it",
    "options": [
      "Vision",
      "Word",
      "Prophesy",
      "Plan"
    ],
    "answer": "Vision",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6d1a9047-9710-4643-a4b9-44f5a0e86928",
    "reference": "16- Zephaniah 1:7 \u201cBe silent in the presence of the LORD God\u201d",
    "question": "Behold, his soul which is lifted up is not upright in him: but the just shall live by his __",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Wisdom",
      "Faith",
      "Understanding"
    ],
    "answer": "Faith",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "aaf5b444-c3b6-40d1-8831-5226243add24",
    "reference": "16- Zephaniah 1:7 \u201cBe silent in the presence of the LORD God\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Zephaniah\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Gedaliah",
      "Cushi",
      "Amariah",
      "Amon"
    ],
    "answer": "Cushi",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5811fd45-aad5-418e-9f90-430207f93bbb",
    "reference": "16- Zephaniah 1:7 \u201cBe silent in the presence of the LORD God\u201d",
    "question": "Which of the following did the Lord say he would sweep away?",
    "options": [
      "The beast",
      "Birds",
      "Fish",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4ba799c6-f70f-455e-a9a9-18da537e11a9",
    "reference": "17- John 6:31-41 \u201cI am the bread which came down from heaven\u201d",
    "question": "Why must we be silent before the Sovereign Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Because he loves us",
      "Because we are full of sins",
      "Because the day of the Lord is near",
      "Because he commands us to be"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the day of the Lord is near",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9d632d1f-3b43-4f39-bdb1-2e2eb996dad4",
    "reference": "17- John 6:31-41 \u201cI am the bread which came down from heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What is the work of God?",
    "options": [
      "To love him",
      "To follow him",
      "To honor him",
      "To believe in the one he has sent"
    ],
    "answer": "To believe in the one he has sent",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d61e3fbd-b1fc-4e33-ac81-f5be3c17a521",
    "reference": "17- John 6:31-41 \u201cI am the bread which came down from heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What gives life to the world?",
    "options": [
      "Fathers",
      "The bread of God",
      "Mothers",
      "Governments"
    ],
    "answer": "The bread of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d48c911c-afbf-4f5c-b30a-1d0b37a2386f",
    "reference": "18- Acts 2:38 \u201cRepent and \u2026 be baptized in the name of Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What does Jesus say he came to do?",
    "options": [
      "Do the will of God",
      "Judge the world",
      "Bless the world",
      "Teach the world"
    ],
    "answer": "Do the will of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "00d9622a-46e2-4cdc-a951-20704ff48814",
    "reference": "18- Acts 2:38 \u201cRepent and \u2026 be baptized in the name of Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What must one do in order to receive the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "Receive Jesus Christ",
      "Go to church",
      "Give to charity",
      "Be kind hearted"
    ],
    "answer": "Receive Jesus Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a65b1aab-c40f-473f-831e-85962b6b0036",
    "reference": "18- Acts 2:38 \u201cRepent and \u2026 be baptized in the name of Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "When will God pour out his Spirit on people?",
    "options": [
      "On the day of Pentecost",
      "In the last days",
      "Whenever he chooses",
      "When we repent"
    ],
    "answer": "In the last days",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "049c8e98-71e9-4948-93df-6a45efad171d",
    "reference": "19- John 3:6 \u201cThat which is born of the Spirit is spirit\u201d",
    "question": "Who will be saved?",
    "options": [
      "Those who call on the name of the Lord",
      "Those who sing to the Lord",
      "Those who pay their tithes and offering",
      "Those who love the Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who call on the name of the Lord",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "826f9545-feb8-414b-af0a-766f4ee56180",
    "reference": "19- John 3:6 \u201cThat which is born of the Spirit is spirit\u201d",
    "question": "Who said \u2018Silver and gold I do not have\u2019?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Peter",
      "Jesus",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Peter",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ab5f1701-8703-4c7d-b61e-8bd8cbea0a3d",
    "reference": "19- John 3:6 \u201cThat which is born of the Spirit is spirit\u201d",
    "question": "What was the reaction of people in the temple as they realized the lame man was healed?",
    "options": [
      "Shocked",
      "Amazed",
      "Frustrated",
      "Jealous"
    ],
    "answer": "Amazed",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "781fcfb6-2766-4278-a536-53e65f571cb4",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:2-6 \u201cFor the law of the Spirit of life in Christ Jesus has made me free from the law of sin and death\u201d",
    "question": "What was the purpose of the believers meeting?",
    "options": [
      "Devotion to the apostles teaching",
      "For the breaking of bread",
      "For prayer",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6dd829f4-9c8d-40b1-8132-fdb83e6aca4a",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:2-6 \u201cFor the law of the Spirit of life in Christ Jesus has made me free from the law of sin and death\u201d",
    "question": "Why is there no more condemnation to those who are in Christ?",
    "options": [
      "Because through Christ sacrifice they are free",
      "They are above the law",
      "They are immune against the law",
      "They can easily fulfill the law"
    ],
    "answer": "Because through Christ sacrifice they are free",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "20f74143-ed36-488a-af93-3f1d31489eeb",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:2-6 \u201cFor the law of the Spirit of life in Christ Jesus has made me free from the law of sin and death\u201d",
    "question": "Why did Christ come to the world?",
    "options": [
      "To judge the world",
      "To be a sin offering",
      "To be life",
      "To teach the world"
    ],
    "answer": "To be a sin offering",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a148a6b5-30ba-4852-b151-b275b71acb92",
    "reference": "21- Acts 2:31-33 \u201c[Christ] having received from the Father the promise of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "What can the mind govern by the spirit be compared to?",
    "options": [
      "Life",
      "a & c",
      "Peace",
      "Death"
    ],
    "answer": "a & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a03dec2-909c-44c8-b643-83936e6a93cd",
    "reference": "21- Acts 2:31-33 \u201c[Christ] having received from the Father the promise of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "Who said \u2018I saw the Lord always before me. Because he is at my right hand, I will not be shaken\u2019?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "David",
      "John",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "David",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3c8325b3-5baf-46ec-9f63-83e382ee8c5d",
    "reference": "21- Acts 2:31-33 \u201c[Christ] having received from the Father the promise of the Holy Spirit\u201d",
    "question": "What did God make Jesus to be?",
    "options": [
      "Lord",
      "Messiah",
      "a & b",
      "Apostle"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7ae278f1-627a-45da-9d79-c61b04e47889",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 12:31-33 \u201cBlasphemy against the Spirit will not be forgiven men\u201d",
    "question": "What must one do to receive the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "b & c",
      "Repent",
      "Be baptized",
      "Be kind"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "840f4878-5e3c-4eed-ac85-d98e335a1579",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 12:31-33 \u201cBlasphemy against the Spirit will not be forgiven men\u201d",
    "question": "Which sin is unforgiving?",
    "options": [
      "Murder",
      "Blasphemy against the Spirit",
      "Lie",
      "Mockery"
    ],
    "answer": "Blasphemy against the Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8822ec74-1040-48a9-90fe-4fdff8cd2254",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 12:31-33 \u201cBlasphemy against the Spirit will not be forgiven men\u201d",
    "question": "How is a tree recognized?",
    "options": [
      "By the season",
      "By the location",
      "By its fruit",
      "By the soil"
    ],
    "answer": "By its fruit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "268eafac-1971-4ff9-b3a9-f3addfb45052",
    "reference": "23-1 John 2:19-27 \u201cBut you have an anointing from the Holy One, and you know all things\u201d",
    "question": "Will we be judged for the word we use?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Only if we blaspheme the Holy Spirit",
      "Yes",
      "Only if we are not believers"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "880b714b-ffec-401d-a7a2-d9d1675a616d",
    "reference": "23-1 John 2:19-27 \u201cBut you have an anointing from the Holy One, and you know all things\u201d",
    "question": "Why can we not both love the world and the father?",
    "options": [
      "Because the things of the world are contrary to God desire for our life",
      "Because God command us not to love the world",
      "Because Satan rules the world",
      "Because Jesus is no longer in the world"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the things of the world are contrary to God desire for our life",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ffbe9aac-970a-4d88-a940-5cc83615261b",
    "reference": "23-1 John 2:19-27 \u201cBut you have an anointing from the Holy One, and you know all things\u201d",
    "question": "Who is a liar?",
    "options": [
      "The president",
      "The government",
      "The politician",
      "Whoever denies Christ"
    ],
    "answer": "Whoever denies Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c2413826-b863-4d4d-863c-d9446c2bd6c4",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 61:1 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD is upon Me, because the LORD has anointed me\u201d",
    "question": "How do we know if we love God?",
    "options": [
      "We go to church",
      "We pay our tithes and offering",
      "We keep his commands",
      "We read his word"
    ],
    "answer": "We keep his commands",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e4c199b7-6f85-4d96-9c91-013ecc137a59",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 61:1 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD is upon Me, because the LORD has anointed me\u201d",
    "question": "Why do we receive the Spirit of God?",
    "options": [
      "To proclaim the good news",
      "To bind up the broken-hearted",
      "To proclaim freedom for the captives",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "20c3493f-560e-40b1-ac96-4102aba32585",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 61:1 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD is upon Me, because the LORD has anointed me\u201d",
    "question": "How will the believers be called?",
    "options": [
      "Priests of the Lord",
      "Children of the Lord",
      "Servants of the Lord",
      "Advocates of the Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "Priests of the Lord",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c10f9e51-0ed7-4135-af06-6a962a63febe",
    "reference": "25- Acts 2:1-18 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit \u2026 your young men shall see visions, your old men shall dream dreams\u201d",
    "question": "Which of the following does the Lord love?",
    "options": [
      "Wrongdoing",
      "Robbery",
      "Justice",
      "Service"
    ],
    "answer": "Justice",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bfe7ad51-be17-4964-9e50-8a56bbb6bf3a",
    "reference": "25- Acts 2:1-18 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit \u2026 your young men shall see visions, your old men shall dream dreams\u201d",
    "question": "When did the Apostles receive the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "When Jesus died",
      "At resurrection",
      "On the day of Pentecost",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "On the day of Pentecost",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d1c9eed0-6944-48ec-8fd5-8198d31550d4",
    "reference": "25- Acts 2:1-18 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit \u2026 your young men shall see visions, your old men shall dream dreams\u201d",
    "question": "What happened when the apostles received the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "They were afraid",
      "They were excited",
      "They began to speak in other tongues",
      "They were bold"
    ],
    "answer": "They began to speak in other tongues",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "abdd1497-de6b-42a1-9bbf-b3c5768a22c3",
    "reference": "26- Joel 2:28 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit on all flesh\u201d",
    "question": "When will God pour out his Spirit on all people?",
    "options": [
      "On judgement\u2019s day",
      "In the last days",
      "On the day of Pentecost",
      "On Christ\u2019s day"
    ],
    "answer": "In the last days",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "732676d2-ef11-462e-996b-9019c9242de7",
    "reference": "26- Joel 2:28 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit on all flesh\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Joel Father\u2019s?",
    "options": [
      "Pethuel",
      "Amos",
      "Jacob",
      "Isaac"
    ],
    "answer": "Pethuel",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "76ba22ac-e8bb-4c99-9e7c-3b5d713f59d3",
    "reference": "26- Joel 2:28 \u201cI will pour out My Spirit on all flesh\u201d",
    "question": "How\u2019s the day of the Lord described as?",
    "options": [
      "Day of darkness",
      "Day of cloud",
      "a & b",
      "Day of peace"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d14fa2b3-a650-4459-81a5-33af3c18564c",
    "reference": "27- 1 Chronicles 12:18-20 \u201cThen the Spirit came upon Amasai\u201d",
    "question": "Fear not, O land; be ___ and rejoice: for the Lord will do great things.",
    "options": [
      "Confident",
      "Grateful",
      "Alert",
      "Glad"
    ],
    "answer": "Glad",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "62aa1675-a6b2-4ceb-8f18-d8cd94bcb1fa",
    "reference": "27- 1 Chronicles 12:18-20 \u201cThen the Spirit came upon Amasai\u201d",
    "question": "If ye be come ___ unto me to help me, mine heart shall be knit unto you.",
    "options": [
      "Peaceably",
      "Loving",
      "Understandably",
      "Supportive"
    ],
    "answer": "Peaceably",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a641d35b-452d-4e1c-afe5-66c27ee66471",
    "reference": "27- 1 Chronicles 12:18-20 \u201cThen the Spirit came upon Amasai\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Amasai?",
    "options": [
      "Apostle",
      "King",
      "Chief of the captains",
      "Prince"
    ],
    "answer": "Chief of the captains",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "93179aa4-7fe1-4a7e-9457-24cc4c1b29e2",
    "reference": "28- Judges 3:10-11 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD came upon him, and he judged Israel\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Jediael\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Ithmah",
      "Eliel",
      "Elnaam",
      "Shimri"
    ],
    "answer": "Shimri",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e7dbfe2b-6857-4492-9eaa-acb3f162b785",
    "reference": "28- Judges 3:10-11 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD came upon him, and he judged Israel\u201d",
    "question": "How long did the land of Aram experience peace before the death of Othniel?",
    "options": [
      "7 years",
      "21 years",
      "40 years",
      "70 years"
    ],
    "answer": "40 years",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8e651681-5671-454d-bcaa-57245924fa90",
    "reference": "28- Judges 3:10-11 \u201cThe Spirit of the LORD came upon him, and he judged Israel\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Othniel\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Ehud",
      "Shamgar",
      "Anath",
      "Kenaz"
    ],
    "answer": "Kenaz",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "03b6a239-c38a-42a9-b393-965468541ada",
    "reference": "29- Ephesians 3:16 \u201cThat He would grant you \u2026 to be strengthened with might through His Spirit in the inner man\u201d",
    "question": "Why did the Lord give Eglon power over Israel?",
    "options": [
      "Because Eglon was faithful to the Lord",
      "Because Eglon won a battle against the Israelites",
      "Because the Israelites did evil",
      "Because the Lord wanted to test Eglon"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the Israelites did evil",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2e1dd99d-7b4a-4021-b0d2-6f520d417c03",
    "reference": "29- Ephesians 3:16 \u201cThat He would grant you \u2026 to be strengthened with might through His Spirit in the inner man\u201d",
    "question": "Wherefore I desire that ye __ not at my tribulations for you, which is your glory",
    "options": [
      "Faint",
      "Cry",
      "Believe",
      "Stumble"
    ],
    "answer": "Faint",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "39b75741-b07b-4a3d-a025-aef433bf4c84",
    "reference": "29- Ephesians 3:16 \u201cThat He would grant you \u2026 to be strengthened with might through His Spirit in the inner man\u201d",
    "question": "Why does God give various gifts to his servants?",
    "options": [
      "So they can show is glory",
      "So they can do miracles",
      "For the edification of the body of Christ",
      "So they can be effective"
    ],
    "answer": "For the edification of the body of Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "095b47fc-9513-4cbb-b957-3b0adcadc778",
    "reference": "29- Ephesians 3:16 \u201cThat He would grant you \u2026 to be strengthened with might through His Spirit in the inner man\u201d",
    "question": "How did Paul become God\u2019s servant?",
    "options": [
      "Through determination",
      "Through baptism",
      "Through reconciliation",
      "By the grace of God"
    ],
    "answer": "By the grace of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b1705575-bc6f-4941-b1b3-9070418ffe21",
    "reference": "30- Mark 14:38 \u201cThe spirit indeed is willing, but the flesh is weak\u201d",
    "question": "Now therefore ye are no more strangers and foreigners, but fellow __ with the saints, and of the household of God.",
    "options": [
      "Believers",
      "Servants",
      "Christians",
      "Citizens"
    ],
    "answer": "Citizens",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "98cd1d6d-cd9a-4207-9569-d71ec2ae7d57",
    "reference": "30- Mark 14:38 \u201cThe spirit indeed is willing, but the flesh is weak\u201d",
    "question": "Apart from praying what else must we do, not to fall into temptation?",
    "options": [
      "Watch",
      "Be zealous",
      "Be honest",
      "Be responsible"
    ],
    "answer": "Watch",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b011dafc-709e-42ae-868c-663b223190ab",
    "reference": "30- Mark 14:38 \u201cThe spirit indeed is willing, but the flesh is weak\u201d",
    "question": "Where did Jesus take Peter, John and James to pray?",
    "options": [
      "Mount of Olives",
      "Mount Sinai",
      "Gethsemane",
      "Synagogue"
    ],
    "answer": "Gethsemane",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ecabdf6b-dc3b-4b0c-83bc-97bddc15cb32",
    "reference": "31- John 4:24 \u201cGod is Spirit, and those who worship Him must worship in spirit and truth\u201d",
    "question": "What were John, Peter and James doing while Jesus was praying?",
    "options": [
      "Worshiping",
      "Praying",
      "Nothing",
      "Sleeping"
    ],
    "answer": "Sleeping",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "50451709-1306-4610-9b24-a7bf51ef63b0",
    "reference": "31- John 4:24 \u201cGod is Spirit, and those who worship Him must worship in spirit and truth\u201d",
    "question": "Where was Jacob\u2019s well?",
    "options": [
      "Samaria",
      "Judea",
      "Jerusalem",
      "Galilee"
    ],
    "answer": "Samaria",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7fc65f72-81a7-487d-b35d-bfdb414fa923",
    "reference": "31- John 4:24 \u201cGod is Spirit, and those who worship Him must worship in spirit and truth\u201d",
    "question": "What did Jesus offer the Samaritan\u2019s woman?",
    "options": [
      "Riches",
      "Wisdom",
      "Living water",
      "Husband"
    ],
    "answer": "Living water",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cf02e247-194c-4ce6-a4fb-55a02181962c",
    "reference": "31- John 4:24 \u201cGod is Spirit, and those who worship Him must worship in spirit and truth\u201d",
    "question": "What did Jesus say his food was?",
    "options": [
      "Manna",
      "Water",
      "Prayer",
      "Doing the will of God"
    ],
    "answer": "Doing the will of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "67b23f3a-5e53-456d-a524-d798fb9362ee",
    "reference": "1- Habakkuk 2:2 \u201cWrite the vision and make it plain\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Habakkuk?",
    "options": [
      "A pastor",
      "A priest",
      "A prophet",
      "A believer"
    ],
    "answer": "A prophet",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "23af9a45-ae50-4281-9454-b406bd08f794",
    "reference": "1- Habakkuk 2:2 \u201cWrite the vision and make it plain\u201d",
    "question": "Where was Habakkuk commanded to write the vision?",
    "options": [
      "In his heart",
      "In a notebook",
      "In the synagogue",
      "On tablets"
    ],
    "answer": "On tablets",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "548855fe-b534-42a9-a3c1-248641428884",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "Who is never at rest?",
    "options": [
      "The Lord",
      "The righteous",
      "Jesus",
      "The enemy"
    ],
    "answer": "The enemy",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7d7330c5-9e61-4b9a-baaa-546c82f94ff9",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "Who was John\u2019s mother?",
    "options": [
      "Mary",
      "Ruth",
      "Elizabeth",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Elizabeth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5452b378-48e9-479e-afeb-f78050cff570",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "What was the name of the angel that appear to Mary?",
    "options": [
      "Justice",
      "Gabriella",
      "Michael",
      "Gabriel"
    ],
    "answer": "Gabriel",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fe1ab29f-fc4f-4c52-b7f2-0cc13842007a",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "What was Mary first reaction when the angel spoke to her?",
    "options": [
      "Excited",
      "Amazed",
      "Troubled",
      "Angry"
    ],
    "answer": "Troubled",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9268fd49-1f2c-4283-b55f-8d7ae4299a46",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "Where does the Lord return people to?",
    "options": [
      "Their country",
      "Their family",
      "Their government",
      "Dust"
    ],
    "answer": "Dust",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f7f9bd9c-3eb5-4360-bb48-f84298433aba",
    "reference": "2- Luke 1:37 \u201cWith God nothing will be impossible\u201d",
    "question": "How is a thousand years like in God sight?",
    "options": [
      "A day",
      "A month",
      "A year",
      "A week"
    ],
    "answer": "A day",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5c6cce99-11ad-4dbc-b814-9b723c12d85f",
    "reference": "4- Matthew 7:12 The Golden Rule",
    "question": "How are the best of our days?",
    "options": [
      "Troublesome",
      "Sorrowful",
      "Exciting",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8da5d7fc-e83e-4e63-8230-123ef268f57d",
    "reference": "4- Matthew 7:12 The Golden Rule",
    "question": "Must we judge others?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "Yes especially those who are lawyers"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "048e6042-4cee-4c00-8f84-38ba0788f0ba",
    "reference": "4- Matthew 7:12 The Golden Rule",
    "question": "Should we give what is sacred to dogs?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "Sometimes",
      "Yes but if we are priests",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b5dd8345-ce58-46bb-971a-9ecb21d45eef",
    "reference": "5- James 2:8 The Royal Law of Scripture",
    "question": "What happens when we keep asking?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "God does not like that attitude",
      "We receive what we asked for",
      "We become slaves"
    ],
    "answer": "We receive what we asked for",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4644b55f-a4f8-4f99-8e16-e54a8865ddb8",
    "reference": "5- James 2:8 The Royal Law of Scripture",
    "question": "How do we know we are doing what is right in God sight?",
    "options": [
      "When we constantly pray",
      "When we give to the poor",
      "When we are kind",
      "When we love our neighbor as ourselves"
    ],
    "answer": "When we love our neighbor as ourselves",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8c9bf9cf-7833-4b0c-9344-6b1afc44299c",
    "reference": "5- James 2:8 The Royal Law of Scripture",
    "question": "Who was James writing to?",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "Gentiles",
      "World",
      "Twelve tribes"
    ],
    "answer": "Twelve tribes",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9e4a8983-ca09-4b28-9f4e-460d34c8418e",
    "reference": "6- Exodus 20:1-17 The Ten Commandments",
    "question": "According to James, should believers show favoritism?",
    "options": [
      "Absolutely",
      "It depends on who we are dealing with",
      "No",
      "Occasionally"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0508e8f4-7877-42d1-8412-a3012b23f768",
    "reference": "6- Exodus 20:1-17 The Ten Commandments",
    "question": "What does God to the land of Egypt as?",
    "options": [
      "Land of guilt",
      "Land of abundance",
      "Land of love",
      "Land of slavery"
    ],
    "answer": "Land of slavery",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d3b1e4ca-7d3d-4c0b-8dcc-0063ccafc099",
    "reference": "6- Exodus 20:1-17 The Ten Commandments",
    "question": "For how many generations can God punish the children for their parents\u2019sin?",
    "options": [
      "Second",
      "Third",
      "Fourth",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e7e25cc1-9583-4a37-96e3-cae9a7142f17",
    "reference": "7- Matthew 22:37-38 \u201cThe first and great commandment\u201d",
    "question": "Which of these is not part of the 10 commandments?",
    "options": [
      "Honor your father and mother",
      "You shall not steal",
      "You shall covet your neighbor\u2019s house",
      "You shall not murder"
    ],
    "answer": "You shall covet your neighbor\u2019s house",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6d67cc58-4d3a-46e3-ab6e-4fe0dc781359",
    "reference": "7- Matthew 22:37-38 \u201cThe first and great commandment\u201d",
    "question": "What is the second commandment?",
    "options": [
      "Honor your father and mother",
      "You shall not steal",
      "Love your neighbor as yourself",
      "You shall not murder"
    ],
    "answer": "Love your neighbor as yourself",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dafdb344-9ca1-4a17-a86f-3a387c7f7f3b",
    "reference": "7- Matthew 22:37-38 \u201cThe first and great commandment\u201d",
    "question": "Whose image was on the denarius?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "God",
      "Caesar\u2019s",
      "The queen"
    ],
    "answer": "Caesar\u2019s",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bdb8991c-8478-4861-aba2-d323e3c88e4e",
    "reference": "8- John 13:34-35 \u201cA new commandment I give to you \u2026 love one another\u201d",
    "question": "Will people marry at resurrection?",
    "options": [
      "Yes but only those who were legally married on earth",
      "No",
      "Yes but only Christians",
      "Yes but only pastors"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1bd7bc61-399c-46df-a9a9-38b510e76596",
    "reference": "8- John 13:34-35 \u201cA new commandment I give to you \u2026 love one another\u201d",
    "question": "How are true disciples recognized?",
    "options": [
      "Through their service in church",
      "Through the love they have for one another",
      "Through their fervent prayers",
      "Through their hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Through the love they have for one another",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7243d5f9-502e-4d92-8565-6e605d297f3c",
    "reference": "8- John 13:34-35 \u201cA new commandment I give to you \u2026 love one another\u201d",
    "question": "What does Jesus say people who believe in him would do?",
    "options": [
      "Greater works than him",
      "Preach",
      "Love one another",
      "Pray without ceasing"
    ],
    "answer": "Greater works than him",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4d709c70-d731-4b15-8aea-bb376dd80e52",
    "reference": "9- John 14:15 \u201cIf you love Me, keep My commandments\u201d",
    "question": "What must believers do if they truly believe in Jesus?",
    "options": [
      "Fear him",
      "Obey his commands",
      "Seek him",
      "Praise him"
    ],
    "answer": "Obey his commands",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b28eec79-488a-4a37-985c-fd5fd49aecac",
    "reference": "9- John 14:15 \u201cIf you love Me, keep My commandments\u201d",
    "question": "Apart from believe in God, who else Jesus command us to believe in?",
    "options": [
      "Our pastors",
      "Our parents",
      "Our governments",
      "Him"
    ],
    "answer": "Him",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2ac826e6-6799-4f82-87bd-a43288eae72e",
    "reference": "9- John 14:15 \u201cIf you love Me, keep My commandments\u201d",
    "question": "Who said \u2018Lord, we don\u2019t know where you are going\u2019?",
    "options": [
      "Peter",
      "James",
      "John",
      "Thomas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thomas",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "01b0d3aa-52dc-4ead-a4fa-035f1f872f0e",
    "reference": "10-  Galatians 5:14 \u201cAll the law is fulfilled in one word\u201d",
    "question": "Jesus says he is?",
    "options": [
      "The way",
      "The truth",
      "The life",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b0c93d4c-a0eb-4a8a-a153-026b3adeb92d",
    "reference": "10-  Galatians 5:14 \u201cAll the law is fulfilled in one word\u201d",
    "question": "Why did Jesus set us free?",
    "options": [
      "For eternity",
      "For service",
      "For freedom",
      "For consecration"
    ],
    "answer": "For freedom",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9280d60a-a2b4-4a26-a4f1-9d4e15aac001",
    "reference": "10-  Galatians 5:14 \u201cAll the law is fulfilled in one word\u201d",
    "question": "According to Paul, does circumcision has any value?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Only if you Jew",
      "Only if you are strong",
      "In some part of the world"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1f672521-b4e3-479d-92fe-35994be80917",
    "reference": "11- Romans 3:19-28 We have the Righteousness of God by Faith in Christ, Not the Law",
    "question": "How can we ensure not to gratify the flesh?",
    "options": [
      "By trusting God",
      "By loving one another",
      "By living by the spirit",
      "By praying regularly"
    ],
    "answer": "By living by the spirit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9afffd31-3ab9-46cc-a8d2-7ed9ff5888e4",
    "reference": "11- Romans 3:19-28 We have the Righteousness of God by Faith in Christ, Not the Law",
    "question": "Who can be declared righteous in God\u2019s sight by works?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "Believers",
      "Jews",
      "Nobody"
    ],
    "answer": "Nobody",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "30393ea8-8f2c-4058-b914-5a08597e7dc0",
    "reference": "11- Romans 3:19-28 We have the Righteousness of God by Faith in Christ, Not the Law",
    "question": "How is righteousness given?",
    "options": [
      "Through love",
      "Through works",
      "Through faith",
      "Through obedience"
    ],
    "answer": "Through faith",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4697ca77-d006-4329-be24-8c5829509f15",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "Is God the God of Jews only?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "No, he is the God of circumcised",
      "No, he is God of the twelve tribes only",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "248f1913-0a22-4107-9414-cd91f3431a8d",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "How did Paul become an apostle?",
    "options": [
      "Through prayer",
      "Through revelation",
      "By the will of God",
      "Through conversion"
    ],
    "answer": "By the will of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "75867fdd-5f77-4817-959d-2d71b1ebe2e0",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "When did God choose us to be his holy people?",
    "options": [
      "When we were born",
      "When we gave our lives to Christ",
      "Before the creation of the world",
      "When we started coming to church"
    ],
    "answer": "Before the creation of the world",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "083d919f-603d-401d-8039-ee8608620d7a",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "What do we need in order to know God better?",
    "options": [
      "A better",
      "Spirit of wisdom",
      "Spirit of revelation",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4725db31-77ab-44d6-ad91-67f6351998ae",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "What are the signs of the beginning of the end time?",
    "options": [
      "Wars",
      "Rumor of wars",
      "Famine and earthquakes",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "655aed4f-37b7-4cfb-a6ec-9ce2cae2acba",
    "reference": "12- Ephesians 2: 1-10 \u201cBy grace you have been saved through faith \u2026 not of works\u201d",
    "question": "Which of the following will not pass away?",
    "options": [
      "The word",
      "Earth",
      "Heaven",
      "Countries"
    ],
    "answer": "The word",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f957691c-18e3-4997-b58d-959904f1b903",
    "reference": "14- John 3:1-18 The New Birth",
    "question": "Who knows the day or hour of the end of the world?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "God, the father",
      "Angels",
      "The disciples"
    ],
    "answer": "God, the father",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5cd6e3db-8ee5-4f72-9c02-de2d234b6f2e",
    "reference": "14- John 3:1-18 The New Birth",
    "question": "What is the meaning of Rabbi?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "Lord",
      "Teacher",
      "Savior"
    ],
    "answer": "Teacher",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d31f017c-a34f-4f93-bdeb-9e9084b267d3",
    "reference": "14- John 3:1-18 The New Birth",
    "question": "What must one do to see the kingdom of God?",
    "options": [
      "Become born again",
      "Pray without ceasing",
      "Be kind",
      "Make sure their \u2018good\u2019 outweighs their \u2018bad\u2019"
    ],
    "answer": "Become born again",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ffe515d3-9d99-4043-bef1-15431619b264",
    "reference": "15- Luke 15:11-32 The Prodigal Son",
    "question": "Who was Nicodemus?",
    "options": [
      "A Samaritan",
      "A merchant",
      "A teacher",
      "A priest"
    ],
    "answer": "A teacher",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bafacee3-e8f6-47e0-9d08-f3213cda7eb2",
    "reference": "15- Luke 15:11-32 The Prodigal Son",
    "question": "What was the father of the prodigal son mood when he saw him coming?",
    "options": [
      "Bitterness",
      "Anger",
      "Dejection",
      "Compassion"
    ],
    "answer": "Compassion",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d2e1864-3baa-4ac9-9f49-829c0e7ac225",
    "reference": "15- Luke 15:11-32 The Prodigal Son",
    "question": "What did the prodigal son say to his father?",
    "options": [
      "I have sinned against heaven",
      "I have sinned against you",
      "a & b",
      "I am happy to see you"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f594d643-b7d2-4a15-aa95-671edd3ad2f2",
    "reference": "16- Matthew 6:25 \u201cDo not worry about your life\u201d",
    "question": "Why did the prodigal son return home?",
    "options": [
      "To visit",
      "To celebrate the Sabbath",
      "To get married",
      "He is had nothing left"
    ],
    "answer": "He is had nothing left",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b6353081-d2db-41f7-93db-5d20afa0f1c2",
    "reference": "16- Matthew 6:25 \u201cDo not worry about your life\u201d",
    "question": "What must we worry about?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Money",
      "Peace",
      "Family"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "02678736-66b8-4dfc-bcc7-d018e5a49a9a",
    "reference": "16- Matthew 6:25 \u201cDo not worry about your life\u201d",
    "question": "Where must we store our treasures?",
    "options": [
      "In the bank",
      "In the stock market",
      "At home",
      "In heaven"
    ],
    "answer": "In heaven",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a41322e-ad2f-4cc2-b73d-0ddfffb5e7a2",
    "reference": "17- Matthew 12:35 The Good Treasure of the Heart",
    "question": "Can anyone serve two masters?",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "Only if we are focus",
      "No",
      "Only if love both equally"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "276eac0e-47ed-477e-9e5c-5ce42374329b",
    "reference": "17- Matthew 12:35 The Good Treasure of the Heart",
    "question": "What awaits a kingdom that is divided against itself?",
    "options": [
      "Success",
      "Victory",
      "Ruined",
      "Unknown"
    ],
    "answer": "Ruined",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "728c89eb-77a1-46e4-bba7-ae5f7ac66b64",
    "reference": "17- Matthew 12:35 The Good Treasure of the Heart",
    "question": "What is the unforgiving sin?",
    "options": [
      "Murder",
      "Lie",
      "Blasphemy against the Holy Spirit",
      "The future"
    ],
    "answer": "Blasphemy against the Holy Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6abe5888-97c6-4a8c-a333-3a4ee12a3f53",
    "reference": "18- Luke 4:1-13 Temptation in the Wilderness",
    "question": "How is a tree recognized?",
    "options": [
      "By the season",
      "By its size",
      "By its location",
      "By its fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "By its fruit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f6d687cc-1770-4923-87ac-4e82bdc8a993",
    "reference": "18- Luke 4:1-13 Temptation in the Wilderness",
    "question": "Where was Jesus before being led by the Holy Spirit into the wilderness?",
    "options": [
      "Israel",
      "Egypt",
      "Jordan",
      "Eden"
    ],
    "answer": "Jordan",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d6b071cd-82a6-442c-a713-8d3ee1156848",
    "reference": "18- Luke 4:1-13 Temptation in the Wilderness",
    "question": "Can man live by bread alone?",
    "options": [
      "No, man needs water as well",
      "No, man needs clothes as well",
      "No, man needs alcohol as well",
      "No, man needs to live by the word of God"
    ],
    "answer": "No, man needs to live by the word of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8de25f29-9226-46af-9e52-3dfe670dcb1f",
    "reference": "19- Luke 6:38 \u201cGive and it will be given to you\u201d",
    "question": "Who alone deserve our worship?",
    "options": [
      "Our parents",
      "God",
      "Musicians",
      "Our government"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1a7acd99-4abf-447d-9c73-a82ea51e45ee",
    "reference": "19- Luke 6:38 \u201cGive and it will be given to you\u201d",
    "question": "What happens if we judge others?",
    "options": [
      "We will be judged also",
      "Nothing",
      "The bible doesn\u2019t say anything about it",
      "We will receive rewards from God"
    ],
    "answer": "We will be judged also",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "15e7c937-954e-40a2-baf0-d887cbff4c79",
    "reference": "19- Luke 6:38 \u201cGive and it will be given to you\u201d",
    "question": "How are the judgments of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "True",
      "Righteous",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "12f7461d-d9a1-42dc-b5d0-2b11191f52b0",
    "reference": "20- John 1:1-14 \u201cThe Word became flesh and dwelt among us, and we beheld His glory\u201d",
    "question": "How is a tree recognized?",
    "options": [
      "By its location",
      "By its size",
      "By its shape",
      "By its fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "By its fruit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "61546904-1eac-455f-bdf5-781ab9dbb0bb",
    "reference": "20- John 1:1-14 \u201cThe Word became flesh and dwelt among us, and we beheld His glory\u201d",
    "question": "What was with God in the beginning?",
    "options": [
      "Angels",
      "Adam",
      "The word",
      "Eve"
    ],
    "answer": "The word",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1cacce54-d98a-40db-a965-834e9424801f",
    "reference": "20- John 1:1-14 \u201cThe Word became flesh and dwelt among us, and we beheld His glory\u201d",
    "question": "How old was John when Jesus was born?",
    "options": [
      "6 months old",
      "1 year old",
      "7 years old",
      "2 months old"
    ],
    "answer": "6 months old",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fa576952-0ab7-44e2-b230-0b61c2516006",
    "reference": "21- John 1:17 \u201cGrace and truth came through Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "Who was the law given through?",
    "options": [
      "Jacob",
      "Isaac",
      "Joseph",
      "Moses"
    ],
    "answer": "Moses",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "daa6ceef-8114-408d-b6a0-a0bf2e1cd2e8",
    "reference": "21- John 1:17 \u201cGrace and truth came through Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the true light that gives light to everyone?",
    "options": [
      "David",
      "John",
      "Jesus",
      "Adam"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4a789d63-52e4-4d2f-ba1b-6e451a08d2b8",
    "reference": "21- John 1:17 \u201cGrace and truth came through Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "Who was John\u2019s mother",
    "options": [
      "Ruth",
      "Mary",
      "Elizabeth",
      "Esther"
    ],
    "answer": "Elizabeth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "933d8127-b980-4215-a0fb-fc774643721f",
    "reference": "22- Romans 2:11 \u201cNo partiality with God\u201d",
    "question": "Who said \u201cI am the voice of one calling in the wilderness\u201d?",
    "options": [
      "Isaiah",
      "Jesus",
      "Elijah",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "Isaiah",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f9593d2f-798e-4195-a241-684eb1d9fa40",
    "reference": "22- Romans 2:11 \u201cNo partiality with God\u201d",
    "question": "How will God judge?",
    "options": [
      "According to the knowledge we have",
      "According to our upbringing",
      "According our deeds",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "According our deeds",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ee33ce35-df53-447d-8529-53487fac688b",
    "reference": "22- Romans 2:11 \u201cNo partiality with God\u201d",
    "question": "Who does not show favoritism?",
    "options": [
      "Judges",
      "Priests",
      "God",
      "Parents"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7e267943-d83f-48fa-bbbf-f73d7300c381",
    "reference": "23- Romans 3:23 \u201cFor all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God\u201d",
    "question": "What will happen to those who sin apart from the law?",
    "options": [
      "Calamity",
      "Nothing",
      "Poverty",
      "They will perish apart from the law"
    ],
    "answer": "They will perish apart from the law",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4fdbd9d2-3005-4a83-8fb2-e805f7b249ba",
    "reference": "23- Romans 3:23 \u201cFor all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God\u201d",
    "question": "Is there any advantage of being Jew in God\u2019s sight?",
    "options": [
      "Yes, for those who live in Israel",
      "No",
      "Yes, for those who still believe in Christ",
      "Yes, for those who are teachers of the word"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0c078898-c394-49bc-b79e-219083ea6005",
    "reference": "23- Romans 3:23 \u201cFor all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God\u201d",
    "question": "Why have never sins?",
    "options": [
      "Jews",
      "Children",
      "Babies",
      "Nobody"
    ],
    "answer": "Nobody",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "adc82225-afcc-442e-a41d-26ad13def403",
    "reference": "23- Romans 3:23 \u201cFor all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God\u201d",
    "question": "What is according to Paul true worship?",
    "options": [
      "Praying without ceasing",
      "Offering oneself to God",
      "Spreading the word of God",
      "Praising God"
    ],
    "answer": "Offering oneself to God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5bc0275e-d65d-44b7-849a-461caf439c48",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "What can we do to know the will of God?",
    "options": [
      "Renew our mind",
      "Have faith",
      "Walk with believers",
      "Go to church"
    ],
    "answer": "Renew our mind",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5f02c9e3-dc39-49bd-936e-359b9f2288c2",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "What does bread represent in the Holy Communion?",
    "options": [
      "The body of Christ",
      "Manna",
      "Sacrifice",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The body of Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2537dea4-8fb5-4f80-9cde-ebd1ae921bbb",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "What does the drink in the Holy Communion represent?",
    "options": [
      "Wine",
      "Alcohol free drink",
      "The blood of Christ",
      "Holy water"
    ],
    "answer": "The blood of Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "acbb6854-2760-4749-b286-b27a5d6c726a",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "Who is the head of every man?",
    "options": [
      "Christ",
      "The pastor",
      "The priest",
      "The church"
    ],
    "answer": "Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bbea1423-faf9-4aeb-abbb-69428874d1f1",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "Which of the following does not define love?",
    "options": [
      "Love is kind",
      "Love is proud",
      "Love is patient",
      "Love is truthful"
    ],
    "answer": "Love is proud",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d6c3681-0ecd-44f3-b679-c338bf680ace",
    "reference": "25- 1 Corinthians 11:24-26 The Holy Communion",
    "question": "Which is the greatest among love, faith, and hope?",
    "options": [
      "Faith",
      "Hope",
      "God",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ab889224-2daa-489c-9f6f-8b4bbfc6b07b",
    "reference": "27- 1 Corinthians 15:33 \u201cEvil company corrupts good habits\u201d",
    "question": "According to Paul between the prophets, apostles and teachers, who come first?",
    "options": [
      "The prophets",
      "The apostles",
      "The teachers",
      "They are equals"
    ],
    "answer": "The apostles",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "35272c1b-be02-441c-8025-2fcc98dd48a1",
    "reference": "27- 1 Corinthians 15:33 \u201cEvil company corrupts good habits\u201d",
    "question": "Why does Paul say he does not deserve to be called an apostle?",
    "options": [
      "Because God didn\u2019t call him",
      "Because he wasn\u2019t among the twelve",
      "Because he persecuted the church",
      "Because he wasn\u2019t fully trained"
    ],
    "answer": "Because he persecuted the church",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "162d9fc0-497b-477e-8e2b-1962d060b135",
    "reference": "27- 1 Corinthians 15:33 \u201cEvil company corrupts good habits\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the firstfruits of those that slept?",
    "options": [
      "Christ",
      "Adam",
      "Eve",
      "Abraham"
    ],
    "answer": "Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0a0c844c-4d26-4373-b7a6-220c23e39975",
    "reference": "28- 2 Corinthians 6:14 \u201cDo not be unequally yoked with unbelievers\u201d",
    "question": "How are we saved?",
    "options": [
      "By obedience",
      "By longsuffering",
      "By works",
      "By grace"
    ],
    "answer": "By grace",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "07b85c79-b198-4de0-85c2-6765ef112272",
    "reference": "28- 2 Corinthians 6:14 \u201cDo not be unequally yoked with unbelievers\u201d",
    "question": "How did God reconcile us to him?",
    "options": [
      "Through petition",
      "Through dedication",
      "Through Christ",
      "Through sanctification"
    ],
    "answer": "Through Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fba08396-acbf-4252-b270-297e87b63945",
    "reference": "28- 2 Corinthians 6:14 \u201cDo not be unequally yoked with unbelievers\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Paul?",
    "options": [
      "A preacher",
      "A teacher",
      "An apostle",
      "Jesus cousin"
    ],
    "answer": "An apostle",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8db19060-6b34-494b-88a0-c5acb66886ba",
    "reference": "29- 2 Corinthians 8:9 Abounding in the Grace of Our Lord Jesus",
    "question": "What must we purify ourselves from?",
    "options": [
      "Desire",
      "Everything that contaminates body and spirit",
      "Hope",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Everything that contaminates body and spirit",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "035cc40c-d422-41c4-8e57-0800ea19cff6",
    "reference": "29- 2 Corinthians 8:9 Abounding in the Grace of Our Lord Jesus",
    "question": "Why did Jesus become poor?",
    "options": [
      "Because he was only preacher the word",
      "Because he didn\u2019t have any proper job",
      "Because he was born in a poor environment",
      "So that we might become rich"
    ],
    "answer": "So that we might become rich",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f8f36db8-b717-4902-86e0-86711821ccf7",
    "reference": "29- 2 Corinthians 8:9 Abounding in the Grace of Our Lord Jesus",
    "question": "Which of the following are expected to excel in?",
    "options": [
      "Faith",
      "Speech",
      "Love",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fa3e4d0b-da29-4651-8376-b26cbc2a1931",
    "reference": "30- Galatians 3:6 \u201cAbraham believed God, and it was accounted to him for righteousness\u201d",
    "question": "How must we not give?",
    "options": [
      "Cheerfully",
      "Generously",
      "Reluctantly",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Reluctantly",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0074973c-438d-41d4-83dd-9235b7ed9275",
    "reference": "30- Galatians 3:6 \u201cAbraham believed God, and it was accounted to him for righteousness\u201d",
    "question": "Who wrote the book of Galatians?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Titus",
      "Peter",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "38f5310d-92eb-4082-95fa-8994046b81b7",
    "reference": "30- Galatians 3:6 \u201cAbraham believed God, and it was accounted to him for righteousness\u201d",
    "question": "How is a person justified?",
    "options": [
      "By grace",
      "By works",
      "By repentance",
      "By petition"
    ],
    "answer": "By grace",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "35d2ffd1-7ab1-4d3e-b4b7-2a434b309b72",
    "reference": "31- Galatians 3:26 \u201cYou are all sons of God through faith in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "Who are Abraham children?",
    "options": [
      "Jacob",
      "Those who have faith",
      "Isaac",
      "Ishmael"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who have faith",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b5fc7f9c-7172-4caf-98de-b1a74b7aa3f4",
    "reference": "31- Galatians 3:26 \u201cYou are all sons of God through faith in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "How does the blessing of Abraham come to the gentiles?",
    "options": [
      "Through prayers",
      "Through fasting",
      "Through Christ",
      "Through worship"
    ],
    "answer": "Through Christ",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1ac7308c-4f8a-4b60-aaea-6a1efa74e463",
    "reference": "31- Galatians 3:26 \u201cYou are all sons of God through faith in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "Now to Abraham and his ___ were the promises made.",
    "options": [
      "Descendants",
      "Children",
      "Seeds",
      "Seed"
    ],
    "answer": "Seed",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ec8e7a7e-f1a8-4c63-a469-1d06b2ef04a7",
    "reference": "31- Galatians 3:26 \u201cYou are all sons of God through faith in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "And if ye be Christ\u2019s, then are ye Abraham\u2019s ___ and heirs according to the promise.",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Seed",
      "Seeds",
      "Descendants"
    ],
    "answer": "Seed",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3ff46aad-d265-46c5-af9f-47b589c7d826",
    "reference": "1- Colossians 1: 9-29 \u201cChrist in you, the hope of glory\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of Colossians?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Joseph",
      "Luke",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ab9fab4d-19e5-40ad-a566-2ef20cb96ef5",
    "reference": "1- Colossians 1: 9-29 \u201cChrist in you, the hope of glory\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the image of the invisible God?",
    "options": [
      "Adam",
      "Jesus",
      "All men",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All men",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "779eb658-7664-4e1f-b2a9-0ad4dc2e4f0c",
    "reference": "2- Philippians 3: 20-21 \u201cOur citizenship is in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "Once you were alienated from God and were enemies in your minds because of your evil behavior. But now he has ______ you by Christ\u2019s physical body through death",
    "options": [
      "saved",
      "redeemed",
      "reconciled",
      "forgiven"
    ],
    "answer": "reconciled",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7988f0f2-249e-4f1f-89ff-f9c69c0307cf",
    "reference": "2- Philippians 3: 20-21 \u201cOur citizenship is in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What was NOT part of Paul's background?",
    "options": [
      "Circumcised the eight day",
      "A Pharisee",
      "An Hebrew of the Hebrews",
      "Of the tribe of Judah"
    ],
    "answer": "Of the tribe of Judah",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fbd62ddb-b8e3-4008-bb5e-eed6d14db627",
    "reference": "2- Philippians 3: 20-21 \u201cOur citizenship is in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What did Paul consider himself to be to the Philippians?",
    "options": [
      "Apostle",
      "Father",
      "Founder",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Apostle",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "75492d77-f9b5-4837-9128-476bcf48a592",
    "reference": "3- Colossians 3:2 \u201cSet your mind on things above\u201d",
    "question": "Who labored with Paul and Clement?",
    "options": [
      "Euodias",
      "Titus",
      "Syntyche",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "a & c",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "309e9c62-8f0f-4342-80d1-43b35836f11e",
    "reference": "3- Colossians 3:2 \u201cSet your mind on things above\u201d",
    "question": "What are Christians expected to do?",
    "options": [
      "Set their eyes on things they can see",
      "Study to show themselves approve to God",
      "Be an example to the believers",
      "Set their hearts on things above"
    ],
    "answer": "Set their hearts on things above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "61acdf9b-a3e7-4bce-83bb-af69010d3015",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 2:5 \u201cLet this mind be in you which was also in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "What is NOT the proper way to obey?",
    "options": [
      "With eye service",
      "With reluctance",
      "As men pleasers",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29295065-a53e-4303-b765-f96e3477c24c",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 2:5 \u201cLet this mind be in you which was also in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "In lowliness of mind let each esteem other ______ than themselves",
    "options": [
      "More noble",
      "Wiser",
      "Better",
      "More worthy"
    ],
    "answer": "Better",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "037b29c4-67fc-4032-8784-c0e4b14a6038",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 2:5 \u201cLet this mind be in you which was also in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "How did Jesus humble himself?",
    "options": [
      "Took upon him the form of a servant",
      "Was made in the likeness of men",
      "Became obedient unto death",
      "Made himself of no reputation"
    ],
    "answer": "Took upon him the form of a servant",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "586cc79a-e6f4-4a4e-93d3-73334812bf99",
    "reference": "5- Philippians 2:16 \u201cHolding fast the word of life\u201d",
    "question": "How should we work out our salvation?",
    "options": [
      "By repenting",
      "By being baptized",
      "By giving to the poor",
      "With fear and trembling"
    ],
    "answer": "With fear and trembling",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0a64b348-c9a6-4f6a-95cd-8a830911afde",
    "reference": "5- Philippians 2:16 \u201cHolding fast the word of life\u201d",
    "question": "Do all things without ________ and disputing?",
    "options": [
      "Murmurings",
      "Envying",
      "Hatred",
      "Backbiting"
    ],
    "answer": "Murmurings",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6e79fe88-5544-4efc-be42-4574bc4cc1d4",
    "reference": "6- Colossians 3:17 \u201cDo Everything in the Name of the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What was Paul's attitude regarding living or dying?",
    "options": [
      "For me to live is Christ, and to die is gain",
      "Let me die the death of the righteous",
      "Naked came I out my mother's womb, and naked shall I return",
      "Though he slay me, yet will I trust in him"
    ],
    "answer": "For me to live is Christ, and to die is gain",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8569a32f-f1cc-4c87-93ab-ac6ddb1bf362",
    "reference": "6- Colossians 3:17 \u201cDo Everything in the Name of the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "And whatsoever you do _________",
    "options": [
      "Do it with your might",
      "Do it heartily, as unto the Lord",
      "Do it in the name of the Lord Jesus, giving thanks to God",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "da3b56b0-f9fe-4815-aec1-9dc40ab064c3",
    "reference": "6- Colossians 3:17 \u201cDo Everything in the Name of the Lord Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What command did Paul give to the wives?",
    "options": [
      "Love your husbands",
      "Love your children",
      "Be a keeper at home",
      "Submit yourselves to your husbands"
    ],
    "answer": "Submit yourselves to your husbands",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0715c79a-021c-4d95-bafa-1d46cf61b60b",
    "reference": "7- Colossians 3:23-25 \u201cDo Everything as to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "What command did Paul give to the wives?",
    "options": [
      "Love your wives",
      "Love your children",
      "Be the provider at home",
      "Submit yourselves to your wives"
    ],
    "answer": "Love your wives",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "010c1dcf-9fd0-432b-b9f3-60af93164d79",
    "reference": "7- Colossians 3:23-25 \u201cDo Everything as to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "What command did Paul give to husbands?",
    "options": [
      "Be an example",
      "Be the head in your home",
      "Provide for your family",
      "Love your wives"
    ],
    "answer": "Love your wives",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "11978fec-62e3-4c4f-9ec5-ee67a6a97cb6",
    "reference": "7- Colossians 3:23-25 \u201cDo Everything as to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "Above all the other good qualities what did Paul say to put on?",
    "options": [
      "Kindness",
      "Meekness",
      "Forgiveness",
      "Charity"
    ],
    "answer": "Charity",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a1d2474e-6aa0-454a-8991-939eed6bcf2c",
    "reference": "8- 1 Thessalonians 1:5 \u201cThe Gospel Comes in Word and Power\u201d",
    "question": "What relationship is mentioned first?",
    "options": [
      "Husband and Wife",
      "Parent and Children",
      "Elders and Deacons",
      "Masters and Servants"
    ],
    "answer": "Husband and Wife",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4b2a5a33-6687-4cda-b3d9-0042f413fe1c",
    "reference": "8- 1 Thessalonians 1:5 \u201cThe Gospel Comes in Word and Power\u201d",
    "question": "Who was with Paul when this epistle was written?",
    "options": [
      "Titus",
      "Timotheus",
      "Silvanus",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5ab8e483-c6b9-42b1-bb30-b8b12b4e05c6",
    "reference": "8- 1 Thessalonians 1:5 \u201cThe Gospel Comes in Word and Power\u201d",
    "question": "For our gospel came NOT unto you in word only, but also in _________",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Love",
      "Faith",
      "Humility"
    ],
    "answer": "Power",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "88f8810f-a5cd-4169-ace6-1ccfd021010d",
    "reference": "8- 1 Thessalonians 1:5 \u201cThe Gospel Comes in Word and Power\u201d",
    "question": "From what did the Thessalonican church turn in order to serve the living and true God?",
    "options": [
      "Devils",
      "Sin",
      "Philosophers",
      "Idols"
    ],
    "answer": "Idols",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cb3068b1-07c6-409c-82e5-75f62165d8f2",
    "reference": "9- 1 Thessalonians 5:11-21 \u201cAlways pursue what is good\u201d",
    "question": "Where had Paul suffered before and was shamefully entreated?",
    "options": [
      "Philippi",
      "Lystra",
      "Antioch",
      "Jerusalem"
    ],
    "answer": "Philippi",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2ed21fa3-dd11-4447-b355-5b31317aea20",
    "reference": "9- 1 Thessalonians 5:11-21 \u201cAlways pursue what is good\u201d",
    "question": "What is the hope of Christians whether dead or alive?",
    "options": [
      "To ever be with the Lord",
      "To live on the new earth",
      "To meet the Lord in the air",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "To ever be with the Lord",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ef5e5529-bc78-41e9-8d64-09b5f21c8b84",
    "reference": "9- 1 Thessalonians 5:11-21 \u201cAlways pursue what is good\u201d",
    "question": "How did Paul describe the coming of the day of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "As travail upon a woman with a child",
      "As a thief in the night",
      "Two shall be in bed, one taken the other left behind",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "As a thief in the night",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a3e83fa1-e6b2-4620-93a5-7f9176cf9b64",
    "reference": "9- 1 Thessalonians 5:11-21 \u201cAlways pursue what is good\u201d",
    "question": "What did Paul urge us to do regarding those that labor among us and are over us in the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Esteem them very highly in love for their work's sake",
      "Know them",
      "Obey them",
      "Compensate them adequately"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f294710a-36bb-47b5-a415-de408ac877e6",
    "reference": "10- 1 Timothy 2:1-5 \u201cPray for Those in Authority\u201d",
    "question": "What did Paul instruct Timothy to charge the Ephesians with?",
    "options": [
      "Reprove, rebuke and exhort",
      "Not live unto themselves, but unto Him who died for them",
      "Teach no other doctrine",
      "Read this epistle to all the brethren"
    ],
    "answer": "Teach no other doctrine",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4aa6e793-5b7e-44d2-9b9e-b6e9086791e1",
    "reference": "10- 1 Timothy 2:1-5 \u201cPray for Those in Authority\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the law for?",
    "options": [
      "For the lawless and disobedient",
      "For the ungodly and sinners",
      "For the Jews",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "For the lawless and disobedient",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c3ad9387-ef1d-4455-ae13-a85cf1316d05",
    "reference": "11- 1 Timothy 4:5 \u201cThings Sanctified by the Word of God and Prayer\u201d",
    "question": "What should be done 'First of all'?",
    "options": [
      "Fasting",
      "Tithing",
      "Prayers",
      "Supplications"
    ],
    "answer": "Supplications",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d3ca3199-a9cf-46ac-be7c-29aca3b1bc56",
    "reference": "11- 1 Timothy 4:5 \u201cThings Sanctified by the Word of God and Prayer\u201d",
    "question": "What is said about a man who desires the position of a bishop?",
    "options": [
      "He should be above reproach",
      "He should discuss this with his wife",
      "He should determine if he was called of God",
      "He should first prove himself as a deacon"
    ],
    "answer": "He should be above reproach",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7c78d378-4143-4acf-8372-9a8ac5b39025",
    "reference": "11- 1 Timothy 4:5 \u201cThings Sanctified by the Word of God and Prayer\u201d",
    "question": "What qualifications were given for a bishop that was NOT required for a deacon?",
    "options": [
      "Rules his house well",
      "Blameless",
      "Given to hospitality",
      "Husband of one wife"
    ],
    "answer": "Given to hospitality",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6c45b878-5330-443d-b77f-31ed75ce1d28",
    "reference": "11- 1 Timothy 4:5 \u201cThings Sanctified by the Word of God and Prayer\u201d",
    "question": "What would the apostles forbid others to do?",
    "options": [
      "Marry",
      "Eat certain foods",
      "Grow beards",
      "Wear wedding rings"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0a870037-5ead-45ec-a955-be29bbcbdc0a",
    "reference": "12- 1 Timothy 6:10 \u201cThe Love of Money: Root of All Evil\u201d",
    "question": "A widow must be at least what age before the church should consider supporting her?",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "50",
      "60",
      "80"
    ],
    "answer": "60",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "af3fbc01-08c0-45aa-9298-629202b3ab68",
    "reference": "12- 1 Timothy 6:10 \u201cThe Love of Money: Root of All Evil\u201d",
    "question": "What does Paul say about laying hands on someone?",
    "options": [
      "Lay hands on the sick and they shall recover",
      "Ordain elders by laying on of hands",
      "It is a basic principle of the doctrine",
      "Do not lay hands on anyone hastily"
    ],
    "answer": "Do not lay hands on anyone hastily",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "05f024c3-33c2-4dfa-8aaf-13b3025dcf78",
    "reference": "13- Deuteronomy 3:22 \u201cGod Himself fights for you\u201d",
    "question": "What can those who desire to be rich fall into?",
    "options": [
      "Snares",
      "Foolish and hurtful lusts",
      "Temptation",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d8c5a566-d22d-42f7-9cfb-e1c6cdc34e80",
    "reference": "13- Deuteronomy 3:22 \u201cGod Himself fights for you\u201d",
    "question": "Whose bed was nine cubits long and four cubits wide?",
    "options": [
      "Balak",
      "Og, king of Bashan",
      "Sihon, king of Heshbon",
      "Agag"
    ],
    "answer": "Og, king of Bashan",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "95512a91-73af-49c3-aaef-8ded0eec1f7e",
    "reference": "13- Deuteronomy 3:22 \u201cGod Himself fights for you\u201d",
    "question": "From where was Moses able to see the land beyond Jordan?",
    "options": [
      "Mount Peor",
      "Mount Pisgah",
      "Mount Ebal",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Mount Pisgah",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "94dd2a70-d345-43dc-bc16-7946e097dac8",
    "reference": "14- Deuteronomy 32:35 \u201cVengeance is Mine\u201d",
    "question": "Israel was not to possess land belonging to whose descendants?",
    "options": [
      "Esau",
      "Lot",
      "Ishmael",
      "Cain"
    ],
    "answer": "Lot",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "df668d97-3453-4107-999a-e037b8617b30",
    "reference": "14- Deuteronomy 32:35 \u201cVengeance is Mine\u201d",
    "question": "What occurred at the inauguration of Joshua?",
    "options": [
      "Thunder and lightning",
      "The pillar of the cloud stood over the door of the tabernacle",
      "The Lord appears in the tabernacle in a pillar of a cloud",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord appears in the tabernacle in a pillar of a cloud",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a497eee2-74c3-4a7f-942e-ca1d10c11107",
    "reference": "14- Deuteronomy 32:35 \u201cVengeance is Mine\u201d",
    "question": "What was wrong with Jeshurun?",
    "options": [
      "Jeshurun lightly esteem the rock of his salvation",
      "Jeshurun waxed fat",
      "Jeshurun forsook God who made him",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Jeshurun forsook God who made him",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ae1e8768-6674-47f6-9be8-068fdeab5459",
    "reference": "15- Jeremiah 30:17 \u201cI will restore health to you\u201d",
    "question": "Where was Moses to die?",
    "options": [
      "Mount Gerizim",
      "Mount Nebo",
      "Mount Pisgah",
      "Mount Peor"
    ],
    "answer": "Mount Nebo",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cc7a746e-ba2e-47a4-9183-464264e6756d",
    "reference": "15- Jeremiah 30:17 \u201cI will restore health to you\u201d",
    "question": "What was Jeremiah to do with the words that the Lord spoke to him?",
    "options": [
      "Deliver them to the king",
      "Write all the words in a book",
      "Declare them to all nations",
      "Keep them in his heart that he might not sin against God"
    ],
    "answer": "Write all the words in a book",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4e308107-e55c-4e2c-a628-b1079282fbf4",
    "reference": "16- 2 Samuel 7: 2-10 \u201cI will appoint a place for My people \u2026 and will plant them\u201d",
    "question": "What did Jeremiah say about Hananiah and his message?",
    "options": [
      "He made people to trust in a lie",
      "He was a fellow prophet of the Lord",
      "The Lord had not sent him",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "He made people to trust in a lie",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7ee8b318-beff-4840-a6fe-c84f97ee6e3d",
    "reference": "16- 2 Samuel 7: 2-10 \u201cI will appoint a place for My people \u2026 and will plant them\u201d",
    "question": "What did David do to the Amalekite who claimed to have killed Saul?",
    "options": [
      "Gave him his daughter to be his wife",
      "Rewarded him with money",
      "Had a young man fall on him and smite him dead",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Had a young man fall on him and smite him dead",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "11a8d1ff-d036-4b17-be46-74b09dff2fea",
    "reference": "16- 2 Samuel 7: 2-10 \u201cI will appoint a place for My people \u2026 and will plant them\u201d",
    "question": "Who did Abner make as king over Israel?",
    "options": [
      "Ishbosheth",
      "Absalom",
      "Doeg",
      "Ittai"
    ],
    "answer": "Ishbosheth",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0c8271a4-59a4-47fa-b384-df64beae6af9",
    "reference": "17- Psalm 37:23 \u201cThe steps of a good man are ordered by the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "How long would David's kingdom endure?",
    "options": [
      "7 years",
      "40 years",
      "Forever",
      "20 years"
    ],
    "answer": "Forever",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ae19bdc0-0e44-488e-8148-cad0e0e32957",
    "reference": "17- Psalm 37:23 \u201cThe steps of a good man are ordered by the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Delight thyself also in the Lord; and he shall give thee ____________________.",
    "options": [
      "Riches",
      "The desires of thy heart",
      "Fame",
      "All your needs"
    ],
    "answer": "The desires of thy heart",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "193ecb31-511d-4042-b6dc-347d1d70f378",
    "reference": "18- Psalm 37:24 \u201cThe LORD upholds him with His hand\u201d",
    "question": "The ____________ borroweth, and payeth not again \u2026.",
    "options": [
      "Poor",
      "Stingy",
      "Wicked",
      "Dishonest"
    ],
    "answer": "Wicked",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e689a83f-1fab-4647-ba80-466dda337ffe",
    "reference": "18- Psalm 37:24 \u201cThe LORD upholds him with His hand\u201d",
    "question": "Sing unto him a new song; play ______ with a loud noise.",
    "options": [
      "Diligently",
      "Fervently",
      "Skilfully",
      "Enthusiastically"
    ],
    "answer": "Skilfully",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "54b3a892-1bd0-4ef7-928f-6920963bdb0e",
    "reference": "19- Romans 7:25 \u201cWith the mind I serve the law of God\u201d",
    "question": "The steps of a __ man are ordered by the Lord; and he delighteth in his way.",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "Bless",
      "Humble",
      "Great"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "085129f4-c8a3-47e9-a455-e62e77dc063f",
    "reference": "19- Romans 7:25 \u201cWith the mind I serve the law of God\u201d",
    "question": "What is the gift of God?",
    "options": [
      "Eternal life",
      "Happiness",
      "Blessings",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Eternal life",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5b578011-fb23-413b-a668-60db700f1b46",
    "reference": "19- Romans 7:25 \u201cWith the mind I serve the law of God\u201d",
    "question": "What would we not know had it not been for the law?",
    "options": [
      "Sin",
      "Righteousness",
      "Holiness",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Sin",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a4303642-6fe1-4faf-9c88-1256959da2b3",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:5-9 \u201cLive According to the Spirit, Not the Flesh\u201d",
    "question": "What law did Paul say he served with his mind?",
    "options": [
      "Law in my members",
      "Law of my mind",
      "Law of sin",
      "Law of God"
    ],
    "answer": "Law of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0f3db482-fd3f-4801-9c3e-8df3c1b11c50",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:5-9 \u201cLive According to the Spirit, Not the Flesh\u201d",
    "question": "How do we fulfill the righteous requirements of the law?",
    "options": [
      "By keeping the ten commandments",
      "By walking in the spirit and not after the flesh",
      "By being circumcised",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By walking in the spirit and not after the flesh",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "adce36de-0bd2-4bd6-b752-babacb7875de",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:5-9 \u201cLive According to the Spirit, Not the Flesh\u201d",
    "question": "What is required to be one of Chris's?",
    "options": [
      "Paying tithes",
      "Assembling yourselves together often",
      "Have the spirit of God dwelling in you",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Have the spirit of God dwelling in you",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "23e0d25b-9edd-472d-b08b-0dfe464fab56",
    "reference": "21- Romans 8:28 \u201cAll things work together for good to those who love God \u2026 according to His purpose\u201d",
    "question": "To be carnally minded is?",
    "options": [
      "Abomination",
      "Terrible",
      "Waste of life",
      "Death"
    ],
    "answer": "Death",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2fc6a484-ac6a-4d08-8918-a67b7c0af2e0",
    "reference": "21- Romans 8:28 \u201cAll things work together for good to those who love God \u2026 according to His purpose\u201d",
    "question": "Who are the sons of God?",
    "options": [
      "Those who are baptized",
      "Those who are believers",
      "As many as are led by the spirit of God",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "As many as are led by the spirit of God",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4e22b1f0-3e6b-43c9-a867-aa689f85c6e9",
    "reference": "21- Romans 8:28 \u201cAll things work together for good to those who love God \u2026 according to His purpose\u201d",
    "question": "For whom do all things work together for good?",
    "options": [
      "Samaritans",
      "Gentiles",
      "Jews",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d2b1f036-9b58-4420-80fb-8f1dd63488c2",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:28-29 \u201cYou are all one in Christ Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What does God also do for those whom he foreknew?",
    "options": [
      "Glorifies",
      "Justifies",
      "Predestinates",
      "Calls"
    ],
    "answer": "Predestinates",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6e71b1da-2ca8-4852-8cd1-fd3e8944b2d4",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:28-29 \u201cYou are all one in Christ Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "What term did Paul use to describe the Galatians?",
    "options": [
      "Unwise",
      "Unworthy",
      "Hypocritical",
      "Foolish"
    ],
    "answer": "Foolish",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "710760fe-e3ef-443f-a228-261da76afe7d",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:28-29 \u201cYou are all one in Christ Jesus\u201d",
    "question": "Who is under the curse?",
    "options": [
      "Gentiles",
      "Jews",
      "As many as rob God of tithes and offerings",
      "As many as are of the works of the law"
    ],
    "answer": "As many as rob God of tithes and offerings",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f6648386-b278-4738-94f7-654bb0891958",
    "reference": "23- Ephesians 1:18-21 \u201cThat you may know \u2026 the hope of His calling\u201d",
    "question": "What have we become if we are in Christ's?",
    "options": [
      "Believers",
      "Heirs according to the promise",
      "Abraham's seed",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b3e5d381-af9a-4933-9941-2b0a47e4b227",
    "reference": "23- Ephesians 1:18-21 \u201cThat you may know \u2026 the hope of His calling\u201d",
    "question": "When were we chosen?",
    "options": [
      "Before the foundation of the world",
      "When we were baptized",
      "When we believed",
      "When we repented"
    ],
    "answer": "Before the foundation of the world",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "79bacbea-2f24-4705-9d0a-60fb1e77419e",
    "reference": "23- Ephesians 1:18-21 \u201cThat you may know \u2026 the hope of His calling\u201d",
    "question": "How have we been sealed?",
    "options": [
      "By the angels",
      "By the blood of Jesus",
      "By the name of Jesus",
      "With the Holy Spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "By the blood of Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "81b9fa54-d4e1-4529-a95e-7a9d89cb343c",
    "reference": "24- Ephesians 2:5-6 \u201cGod Raised Us Up Together with Christ\u201d",
    "question": "In what position is Christ?",
    "options": [
      "The head over all things",
      "In the heavenly places",
      "Far above all principality, power, might, dominion, and name",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6f1ec515-66fd-4132-bac3-7c3f6f90ef44",
    "reference": "24- Ephesians 2:5-6 \u201cGod Raised Us Up Together with Christ\u201d",
    "question": "Where have you been made to sit?",
    "options": [
      "Far off",
      "In the church",
      "In heavenly places",
      "At the right hand of the father"
    ],
    "answer": "In heavenly places",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a05945ad-510c-41fe-94fd-be8a534cdffe",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 62:1 \u201cMy soul silently waits for God\u201d",
    "question": "We all had our conversation in times past in the lusts of our flesh, fulfilling the desires of the flesh and of the mind; and were by nature the children of ________________, even as others.",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "Adam",
      "Wrath",
      "Iniquity"
    ],
    "answer": "Wrath",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "40a0b768-42d5-4cbb-9ffc-02ee4394234d",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 62:1 \u201cMy soul silently waits for God\u201d",
    "question": "Lead me to ______ that is higher than I. For thou hast been a shelter for me...",
    "options": [
      "The rock",
      "Zion",
      "Jerusalem",
      "The Temple"
    ],
    "answer": "The rock",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b117981c-c3b7-4728-a783-e0b4e5205ebc",
    "reference": "25- Psalm 62:1 \u201cMy soul silently waits for God\u201d",
    "question": "_____ him at all times; ye people, pour out your heart before him....",
    "options": [
      "Pray to",
      "Trust in",
      "Obey",
      "Honor"
    ],
    "answer": "Trust in",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "60ca07ef-7a59-42c7-9eff-e70aa0184b2d",
    "reference": "26- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is my light and my salvation\u201d",
    "question": "Because thy ___________- is better than life, my lips shall praise thee.",
    "options": [
      "Mercy",
      "Forgiveness",
      "Faithfulness",
      "Loving kindness"
    ],
    "answer": "Loving kindness",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "44dc9dee-31fb-407d-857c-dc553b76a2c6",
    "reference": "26- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is my light and my salvation\u201d",
    "question": "Let integrity and uprightness _____ me; for I wait on you.",
    "options": [
      "Preserve",
      "Reward",
      "Instruct",
      "Deliver"
    ],
    "answer": "Preserve",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "42db63d8-376b-42d8-acb3-4ad44ee57748",
    "reference": "27- Isaiah 55:12 \u201cYou shall go out with joy and be led out with peace\u201d",
    "question": "One thing have I desired of the Lord, that will I seek after; that I may ______ all the days of my life",
    "options": [
      "Be holy",
      "Keep His commandments",
      "Dwell in the house of the Lord",
      "Be an example to the believers"
    ],
    "answer": "Dwell in the house of the Lord",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "54f36552-b949-4ad4-9e7b-4d0bfa8c4f38",
    "reference": "27- Isaiah 55:12 \u201cYou shall go out with joy and be led out with peace\u201d",
    "question": "How do our thoughts compare to God's thoughts?",
    "options": [
      "As a grain of sand on a seashore",
      "As a drop in a bucket",
      "As a minnow in the ocean",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "488fde08-2fef-4420-a425-02c54eb16e60",
    "reference": "28- John 14:18 \u201cI will not leave you orphans; I will come to you\u201d",
    "question": "What will not return void?",
    "options": [
      "God's word",
      "God's spirit",
      "Our prayers",
      "Our gifts"
    ],
    "answer": "God's word",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f2ce37f2-f8d2-413a-b254-334ef29894de",
    "reference": "28- John 14:18 \u201cI will not leave you orphans; I will come to you\u201d",
    "question": "By what did Jesus say others would know who were his disciples?",
    "options": [
      "Their faithfulness in attending the temple",
      "Their dedication to basic principles such as prayer",
      "Their love toward one another",
      "Their outward appearance"
    ],
    "answer": "Their love toward one another",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b3c0ef42-149a-445d-a88b-2cd43b02a1cd",
    "reference": "28- John 14:18 \u201cI will not leave you orphans; I will come to you\u201d",
    "question": "How did Jesus reply to Philip's request \u201cLord, show us the Father\u201d?",
    "options": [
      "I am come in my Father's name",
      "I and my Father are one",
      "The fulness of the Godhead dwells in me bodily",
      "He that has seen me has seen the Father"
    ],
    "answer": "He that has seen me has seen the Father",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a92117ad-40b0-4adf-bd61-b7c87df7b577",
    "reference": "29- 1 John 1:7 \u201cWe have fellowship with one another\u201d",
    "question": "What did Jesus say would do if we loved him?",
    "options": [
      "Read His word",
      "Pray",
      "Witness",
      "Keep His commandments"
    ],
    "answer": "Keep His commandments",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3cc29738-ab9b-47cb-89b4-cce2d78c3231",
    "reference": "29- 1 John 1:7 \u201cWe have fellowship with one another\u201d",
    "question": "Why did John write this epistle?",
    "options": [
      "To warn against seducers",
      "That you sin not",
      "That your joy may be full",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "That your joy may be full",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "38c97f4f-0623-40af-a5e6-2f2278a437a1",
    "reference": "29- 1 John 1:7 \u201cWe have fellowship with one another\u201d",
    "question": "In this epistle what did John say that God is that began with the letter \u201cL\u201d?",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Light",
      "Lamb of God",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Light",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bf4da70e-82bc-4d35-9e86-63b6b0a88d55",
    "reference": "30- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "What types of people did John call a liar or one who lies?",
    "options": [
      "Those that deny that Jesus is come in the flesh",
      "Those that say they have not sinned",
      "Those that say they know him but do not keep his commandments",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Those that say they have not sinned",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f8e5b140-7af0-40c8-93eb-7ed0815e2a6a",
    "reference": "30- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "But the ___________ are like the troubled sea, when it cannot rest, whose waters cast up mire and dirt.",
    "options": [
      "Persecuted",
      "Unbelievers",
      "Wicked",
      "Backsliders"
    ],
    "answer": "Wicked",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c1f2cdd1-50c4-4685-aafd-7012f9e7f1cf",
    "reference": "30- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "Why should we fast?",
    "options": [
      "To give your bread to the hungry",
      "To clothe the poor",
      "To loose the bands of wickedness",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "To loose the bands of wickedness",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e8789894-359d-4f2d-965e-5300fa8ca761",
    "reference": "30- Isaiah 55:6 \u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found\u201d",
    "question": "For a small moment have I forsaken thee; but with great __will I gather thee.",
    "options": [
      "Mercies",
      "Love",
      "Wonder",
      "Thunder"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercies",
    "quarter": "Q3",
    "month": ""
  }
]